EmEditor Plug-in  ToTraditionalChinese  Version 5.00
Emurasoft, Inc.
https://www.emeditor.com/

ENGLISH

This plug-in can convert the selected Simplified Chinese text into 
Traditional Chinese text.

Select the text you want to convert, and run this plug-in. It will 
convert the selected text into Simplified Chinese.

JAPANESE

このプラグインは選択した簡体字中国語を繁体字中国語に変換します。

変換したいテキストを選択して、このプラグインを実行してください。選択さ
れたテキストを繁体字中国語に変換します。

HISTORY

Version 1.00  (15 Oct 2001)
- Initial version

Version 1.01  (10 Jan 2002)
- Added large icons, 256-color and true color icons for toolbars.

Version 5.00  (20 Dec 2005)
- EmEditor Version 5.00 support.

